welcome everyone to the fifth of the
欢迎大家参加第五届
five jigsaw talks project jigsaw under
五个拼图谈判项目下的拼图
the hood quick poll who has been to all
曾经去过的引擎盖快速民意调查
five some a small number of hands okay
五只少量的手还可以
so people have fought okay yes yes yes
人们已经战斗好了是是是
so people have this is a serious
所以人们有一个严重的
question people have been picking and
问题人们一直在采摘，
choosing when we've had a sequence of
选择何时我们有一系列
jigsaw talks people have been picking
人们一直在拼图游戏
and choosing which ones to go to yes
然后选择要去的
okay interesting we all we have another
好吧，有趣的是，我们所有人都有另一个
five-star we have 25 * attendees at the
五星级，我们有25 *参加者
front I think you've probably been to
前我想你可能去过
all five one of them twice up a now
他们五个全部一次两次
you're in the fifth one let's go with
你在第五个，让我们一起去
them ok so anyway my name is Alex
他们还可以，所以我叫亚历克斯
Buckley I work in the Java platform
Buckley我在Java平台上工作
group at Oracle and this is the deep
甲骨文团队，这是最深的
dive behind the scenes under the hood
潜入幕后
what's really going on with class
课堂上到底发生了什么
loaders in jeddah canine that tries to
吉达犬的装载机试图
explain some of the some of the
解释一些
statements you may have heard in other
您可能在其他人听到的陈述
talks talking about the the jets that
谈论谈论喷气式飞机
are in jdk 9 sometimes some statements
在jdk 9中有时会有些陈述
are made that seem to be a bit confusing
看起来有点混乱
and i hope this talk will explain what's
我希望这个演讲能解释什么
really going on so in jdk nine but it
真的在jdk九中进行了，但是
stand alone so i still need to introduce
独立存在，所以我仍然需要介绍
that in jdk nine the main feature is the
在JDK 9中，主要功能是
module system the let's code be more
模块系统让我们的代码更多
reliable and maintainable we've used the
可靠且可维护，我们使用了
module system to turn the monolithic JDK
模块系统转向单片JDK
into the modular JDK that is breaking up
进入正在分解的模块化JDK
the RT jar file inside the JDK into
将JDK中的RT jar文件放入
dozens of reusable modules jdk 9 also
数十个可重用模块jdk 9也
has small enhancements to the Java
对Java有一些小的增强
language and somewhat larger
语言和更大
enhancements to the standard labors plus
加强标准劳动，再加上
Javadoc gets a search box and JDK via J
Javadoc通过J获取搜索框和JDK
shell includes a ripple at last round of
外壳在最后一轮中包含波纹
applause I can I can hear
掌声我能听到
in my head ah so project X or is a
在我的头上啊，所以项目X还是一个
project led by Oracle in OpenJDK it's
由Oracle在OpenJDK中领导的项目
the container for all of our work
我们所有工作的容器
building a module system and
建立一个模块系统
modularizing the JDK we're standardizing
模块化我们正在标准化的JDK
the module system in the java community
java社区中的模块系统
process through jsr 376 and we're
通过jsr 376处理，我们
standardizing the structure of the
规范结构
modular JDK in the java community
Java社区中的模块化JDK
process through the umbrella jsr for
通过伞jsr处理
java SE 9 so when you use JDK 9 you're
Java SE 9，因此当您使用JDK 9时
always subject to the rules of the
始终遵守
module system that's what's under the
模块系统就是
hood and it's what most of this talk is
引擎盖，这就是本讲的大部分内容
about they'll touch on some aspects some
关于他们将涉及一些方面
of the impact of the modular JDK in near
模块化JDK在附近的影响
the end this talk has four parts the
最后，本演讲分为四个部分
first part explains how the module
第一部分解释模块
system works with the java language and
系统与Java语言一起使用，并且
vm to improve the reliability of your
vm提高您的可靠性
code the second part is really about
代码第二部分是关于
migrating to modules the third part
迁移到模块第三部分
explains what the module system is
解释什么是模块系统
fundamentally capable of beyond what you
根本有能力超越你
can express in the java language and the
可以用Java语言和
fourth part is about the road to jdk
第四部分是关于通往jdk的道路
nine and some of the things you should
九，有些事情你应该
watch out for while traveling on it so
在旅行时要当心
first part everyone knows the hierarchy
第一部分，每个人都知道层次结构
of accessibility in the java language
语言的可访问性
and vm it's simple to understand easy to
和vm易于理解，易于理解
use and strongly enforced by the
使用并强烈执行
compiler and vm but it has a big
编译器和虚拟机，但它有一个很大的
weakness the only way to share code
弱点是共享代码的唯一方法
between packages is with public but then
包之间是公共的，但是
you're sharing with everyone it's not
与所有人共享不是
surprising that package friendship in
令人惊讶的包装友谊
one form or another has been requested
已要求一种或另一种形式
many times over the years one goal of
这些年来，一个目标
the module system is strong
模块系统坚固
encapsulation to allow a component to
封装以允许组件
declare which of its public types are
声明其公共类型是
accessible to other components and which
其他组件可以访问的
are not the lines in italic are the
不是斜体字的线是
levels of acts
行为水平
ability in Jerry canine connected with
杰里犬的能力与
the module system reading upwards you
模块系统向上读取
can arrange for public types to be
可以安排公共类型
accessible only within their module or
只能在其模块内访问或
accessible within their module and two
在他们的模块和两个
other specific friend modules or
其他特定的朋友模块或
accessible to everyone as was injured he
每个人都可以接近，因为他受伤了
ate so as usual migration drives a lot
吃了点东西，因为通常的迁移驱动了很多
of our thinking we want to make it easy
我们想让我们轻松一点
to place an existing package into a
将现有的包装放入
module and immediately give that package
模块并立即提供该软件包
the benefit of strong encapsulation we
强封装的好处我们
don't want each and every public type in
不想每个公共类型
a package to have to opt-in to strong
必须选择加入强
encapsulation so public types in a
封装，以便将公共类型
package are not accessible outside the
包不能在外部访问
module by default that is public on a
默认情况下，该模块在
type declaration no longer means
类型声明不再意味着
everyone can access the type what
每个人都可以访问类型
happens if someone tries to access a
如果有人尝试访问
public type that's not accessible here's
在这里无法访问的公共类型
a slightly aging but very interesting
稍微老化但很有趣
example from glassfish 4.1 at the time
当时来自glassfish 4.1的示例
of screen grabbing it didn't start on
屏幕抓取未开始
jdk nine because the vm through an
jdk的九个因为vm通过
illegal access error I don't expect
我没想到有非法访问错误
you'll be able to read the the ring text
您将能够阅读铃声文本
but it says illegal access error class
但它说非法访问错误类
Khamsin enterprise security provide a
康信企业安全提供了
policy rapper in unnamed module don't
未命名模块中的策略说唱歌手不要
worry about that yet cannot access class
担心却无法上课
Sun security provider policy file in
中的Sun安全提供程序策略文件
module Java base the point is that the
Java模块的基础是
class sons security provider policy file
子级安全提供程序策略文件
is declared public but since it's a jdk
被宣布为公开，但由于它是jdk
internal API it's now accessible only
内部API，现在只能访问
within the Java base module sorry
Java基本模块中的对不起
glassfish you need to find an
您需要找到一个玻璃鱼
alternative security API
替代安全API
in jdk nine modules are first class
在jdk中，九个模块是一流的
program components like classes and
程序组件，例如类和
interfaces here's the declaration of the
接口是这里的声明
java sequel module that contains JDBC
包含JDBC的Java续集模块
it's in a file called module info java
它在名为module info java的文件中
in a directory named after the module
在以模块命名的目录中
javed or sequel the compiler treats this
厌倦或续集的编译器对待
like any other java file and translates
像其他任何Java文件一样进行翻译
it to module in photo class which you
它到你的照相课中的模块
can put in a jar file as normal we would
可以像往常一样放入jar文件
call that a modular jar the package
称模块罐为包装
hierarchy exists in the same directory
层次结构存在于同一目录中
source java sequel as module info java
源Java续集作为模块信息java
so module effort at java is outside of
所以Java的模块工作不在
all of the packages in the module that's
该模块中的所有软件包
because it's the job of the module
因为这是模块的工作
declaration to say whether a package is
声明是否包装
strongly encapsulated or not it's easy
高度封装或不容易
to get strong encapsulation for the
获得强大的封装
types in your packages don't mention the
包裹中的类型不要提及
package in the module declaration to
包中的模块声明为
allow other modules to access one of
允许其他模块访问其中之一
your packages or more specifically the
您的包裹，或更具体地说
public types of your package just add
您包的公开类型只需添加
and exports clause as I said you can
和出口条款，正如我所说，您可以
export to all other modules as is
照原样导出到所有其他模块
happening here or you can say exports to
发生在这里，或者您可以说出口到
to give access to only your friend
只允许访问您的朋友
modules at compile time Java Sea
Java Sea编译时的模块
prevents code outside the Java sequel
防止Java续集之外的代码
module from accessing the public types
访问公共类型的模块
of any packages in it except for those
除了其中的任何软件包
three packages listed you get the same
列出的三个包您得到相同的
compile time error as when you try to
尝试时编译时间错误
access a package private type from
从访问包私有类型
outside it's packaged in J decades and
在几十年的时间里包装
then at runs if you somehow built the
然后在运行时，如果您以某种方式构建了
class files by hand at runtime a runtime
在运行时手动生成类文件
the vm throws an illegal access error
虚拟机引发非法访问错误
like you saw with glassfish if you try
就像您尝试用玻璃鱼看到的一样
to access the public types of anything
访问任何事物的公共类型
except those three packages let's dive
除了那三个包，让我们潜入
into the vm more deeply traditionally
传统上更深入地进入虚拟机
accessibility in the Java platform is
Java平台中的可访问性是
about who is doing the access and what
关于谁在进行访问以及执行什么操作
is the public protected private flag on
是受公共保护的私人标志
the target class at runtime the vm uses
vm使用的运行时目标类
the class loader of the accessing class
访问类的类加载器
to find and load the target class
查找并加载目标类
and then the vm checks the flag public
然后虚拟机检查标志public
protected private of that target class
受保护的私有对象
now because the vm relies on class
现在，因为虚拟机依赖于类
loaders people can create loaders that
装载机的人们可以创建装载机
only know how to find and load classes
只知道如何查找和加载类
of certain packages in effect loaders
效果加载程序中某些软件包的数量
can isolate one package from another in
可以将一个包装与另一个包装隔离
the top picture class PC is trying to
顶级图片类PC试图
access class QD the loader for PC knows
PC加载程序知道的访问类QD
to delegate it just just bear with me it
委托给我就好了
knows to delegate to another loader for
知道委托给另一个装载者
any class in package Q such as QD only
包Q中的任何类，例如仅QD
when that other loader has found loaded
当其他装载者发现装载时
QD can the vm check its flags to
QD可以让vm检查其标志以
determine if it's public enough for POC
确定它是否对POC足够公开
to access it now in the bottom picture
现在可以在底部的图片中访问它
the loader for PC has no idea where to
PC的加载器不知道在哪里
find package Q so no access to QD is
找到包Q，因此无法访问QD
possible from PC technically this isn't
从技术上讲这可能不是从PC
a failure of accessibility since the vm
自vm以来的可访问性失败
never actually gets to load never gets
从来没有真正加载
to check the flags of QLD instead it's a
检查QLD的标志，而是
failure of visibility QD is invisible to
可见性故障QD对
PC because the class loading couldn't
PC，因为无法加载课程
find QD still the effect is quite
发现QD效果还是蛮不错的
powerful if the class loader of the
功能强大，如果
accessing class cannot find and
访问类猫找不到和
load the target class then it doesn't
加载目标类，然后它不会
matter if the target class is public
目标类别是否公开是很重要的
it's effectively encapsulated so whoever
它被有效地封装，无论谁
sets up the class loaders sets up this
设置类加载器来设置
effective encapsulation the thing is
有效封装的东西是
though that encapsulation based on class
尽管基于类的封装
loaders is not strong encapsulation
装载机封装不牢固
sadface it relies on packages being
sadface它依赖于软件包
carefully apportioned into different
仔细分配到不同
loaders but that isn't how the JDK has
加载程序，但JDK并非如此
ever worked most code in the JDK is
在JDK中曾经工作过的大多数代码是
loaded by the bootstrap or platform
由引导程序或平台加载
class loaders while code on the
类加载器，而代码在
classpath all of it is loaded by the
classpath全部由
application class loader spinning up
应用程序类加载器旋转起来
lots of loaders for all of this codes to
所有这些代码的装载机
try and isolate it and to try
尝试将其隔离并尝试
encapsulated would be a compatibility
封装将是兼容性
nightmare and in any case there is no
噩梦，无论如何都没有
actual isolation you can circumvent
您可以规避的实际隔离
class loaders by getting hold of
通过掌握类加载器
references to java.lang.class objects
对java.lang.class对象的引用
which you can always do for any object
您可以随时为任何对象执行的操作
and then once you have a class object
然后有了一个类对象
the class loaders are irrelevant and
类加载器是无关紧要的，
it's impossible to stop references to
不可能停止引用
class objects from being passed around
类对象不被传递
strong encapsulation is about being able
强大的封装能力
to prevent access even if the accessing
防止访问，即使访问
class and the target class are in the
类和目标类在
same class loader such as the
相同的类加载器，例如
application class loader and even if
应用程序类加载器，即使
someone is using core reflection to
有人正在使用核心反射
manipulate class objects so let's assume
操作类对象，所以让我们假设
that multiple modules are somehow mapped
以某种方式映射了多个模块
to the same class loader can clasp you
到同一个类加载器可以让你紧扣
see in module X access QD in module y
参见模块X中的访问QD模块中的QD
another goal of the module system is
模块系统的另一个目标是
reliable dependencies to replace the
可靠的依赖关系来取代
brittle error-prone classpath mechanism
易碎的易错类路径机制
with a means for program components to
用程序组件的方式
declare explicit dependencies on one
声明对一个的显式依赖
another so in order for PC to access QD
以便PC访问QD
not only does module y need to export
不仅模块y需要导出
package q but module X needs to somehow
包q但模块X需要某种方式
explicitly depend on module why the
明确取决于模块为何
formal name that depends on is
依赖的正式名称是
readability readability underpins
可读性可读性的基础
accessibility in the Java language and
Java语言的可访问性和
vm in 9 the accessing class PC must be
9中的vm，访问类PC必须是
in a module that reads the module of the
在一个模块中读取
target class that is reads module why
读取模块的目标类为何
and the module containing the target
和包含目标的模块
class must export its package to at
类必须将其包导出到
least the module of the accessing class
至少是访问类的模块
so accessibility is a two-way street at
因此可访问性是一条位于
module X reads module y a module y
模块X读取模块ya模块y
exports this interesting package q to at
将此有趣的包q导出到
least x
至少x
note with these arrows that
注意这些箭头
accessibility is independent of class
可访问性与类无关
loaders I don't need to talk about the
装载机，我不需要谈论
class Otis on this slide just like
像这张幻灯片上的Otis类
accessibility was before the module
可访问性在模块之前
system this is important for two reasons
系统很重要，有两个原因
it means accessibility works at compile
这意味着可访问性在编译时有效
time when there aren't any class loaders
没有任何类加载器的时间
second it means you can reason about
其次，这意味着您可以推理
accessibility based solely on the
可访问性完全基于
requires and exports clauses in module
模块中的require和export子句
in photo Java files there's no need to
在Java照片文件中，无需
worry about which class loaders will
担心哪些装载机会
come into existence a runtime in fact
实际上存在一个运行时
the exports part of accessibility is
可访问性的出口部分是
fairly straightforward packages either
相当简单的软件包
exported or it isn't but on readability
导出，或者不是，但可读性强
there's more to say when you depend on a
当您依靠一个
module you depend on a hopefully
您希望依靠的模块
coherent set of packages that are
连贯的软件包集
exports that's its surface in some sense
从某种意义上说出口就是表面
those packages are the interface of the
这些软件包是
module inside the module hundreds more
模块内的模块数以百计
packages may sit strongly encapsulated
包可能被牢固地封装
not exported not for you waiting to help
没有导出不为您等待帮助
implement that interface and more than
实现该接口
that when you depend on a module um you
当你依赖一个模块
indirectly depend on all of the modules
间接依赖于所有模块
it depends on for example if you depend
这取决于例如你是否依赖
on the Java activation module in the JDK
在JDK中的Java激活模块上
with its 35 classes then you indirectly
有35个班级，那么您间接地
depends on the Java desktop module in
取决于Java桌面模块
the jdk with its 5835 classes if the
jdk及其5835类，如果
watchword for JDK 8 was functional then
当时，JDK 8的口号已经开始运作
for JD k9 the watchword is transitive
对于JD k9，该标语是可传递的
you should think in terms of the set of
你应该考虑一套
modules needed transitively by your
您的传递需要的模块
application that is the indirect
间接的应用程序
dependences can be as important as the
依赖可能与
direct dependencies let's see how
直接依赖关系让我们看看如何
readability models this I'll use an
可读性模型，我将使用
example of readability from the graph of
图表的可读性示例
JDK modules the Java sequel module that
JDK将Java续集模块
holds JDBC requires the Java login
持有JDBC需要Java登录
module that exports the package
导出包的模块
java.util logging
java.util日志记录
this requires Clause means that code in
这需要条款意味着
the Java sequel module can access the
Java续集模块可以访问
public types of Java util logging such
Java util日志记录的公共类型，例如
as logger you can see that some code in
作为记录器，您可以看到其中的一些代码
the JDBC driver manager class on the
上的JDBC驱动程序管理器类
left is newing an instance of lager fine
左是更新一个更大的罚款实例
what if it was the API of the Java
如果是Java的API怎么办
sequel module rather than its
续集模块而不是其
implementation that wants to use the
想要使用
logotype in other words locket is in a
换句话说，小盒上的标识
method signature a public method
方法签名公共方法
signature author of a public interface
公共接口的签名作者
in an exported package so what if that
在导出的包中，如果那样
API wants to refer to the logotype
API要引用标识
rather than some method body so here the
而不是某些方法主体，所以这里
JDBC driver interface wants to return a
JDBC驱动程序接口要返回一个
logger let's look at this through the
记录器让我们通过
eyes of an application module that uses
使用的应用程序模块的眼睛
JDBC my app in order to use the dry it
JDBC我的应用程序为了使用它干
to call that driver method that returns
调用返回的驱动程序方法
a logger the my app module not only
记录器不仅是我的应用程序模块
needs to read the Java sequel module but
需要阅读Java续集模块，但是
also the Java logging module which
还有Java日志记录模块
exports logger it would be a pain if the
出口记录器，如果
developer of my app had to remember to
我的应用程序的开发人员必须记住
say requires java logging when using a
说当使用
particular part of the api of java
Java api的特定部分
sequel sadface there's good news the
续集悲伤的面孔有个好消息
java sequel module can take on the
java续集模块可以承担
responsibility of remembering look at
记住看的责任
the java sequel module it now says
现在说的Java续集模块
requires transitive java dot logging the
需要传递Java点记录
word transitive here means that anyone
这里的“可及”一词意味着任何人
who reads the java sequel module also
谁也阅读Java续集模块
reads the java logging module for free
免费读取Java日志记录模块
the my app module no longer has to
我的应用模块不再需要
bother with requires java logging
麻烦需要Java日志记录
because it reads java logging thanks to
因为它读取Java日志记录，这要归功于
reading java sequel happy face this is
读java续集笑脸这是
called implied readability and it's very
称为隐式可读性，这非常
powerful it's powerful because it lets a
功能强大，功能强大，因为它可以让
module be refactored without breaking
重构模块而不中断
consumers for example suppose that Java
例如，消费者假设Java
logging
测井
has some auxiliary packages that we'd
有一些辅助软件包，我们会
like to start shipping in a separate
喜欢开始单独发货
module log extras stuff in it some
模块日志额外的东西在其中一些
exports the Java logging module can say
导出Java日志记录模块可以说
requires transitive Java requires
需要传递Java需要
transitive log extras so that my app
传递日志附加功能，以便我的应用
which already implicitly reads Java
已经隐式读取Java
logging also implicitly reads log extras
日志记录还隐式读取日志附加内容
my app would be unaware that this
我的应用程序不会意识到
refactoring down the stack is happening
向下进行堆栈重构
it just says requires java sequel so in
它只是说需要Java续集，所以在
essence this model of readability
本质上就是这种可读性模型
supports downward decomposition any
支持向下分解
module you read can be decomposed by its
您阅读的模块可以被其分解
author into new modules and readability
编写新模块并提高可读性
of the new modules can be recovered with
的新模块可以使用
a requires transitive clause in the old
在旧版本中需要一个及物从句
module so you can see that the the
模块，因此您可以看到
definition of reads one module reading
读取的定义一个模块的读取
another is recursive a module X reads
另一个是X读取的递归模块
another module Y by requiring it
通过要求另一个模块Y
directly with a requires clause or by
直接与require子句或
reading some third module q there's the
读一些第三个模块q
recursion reading some third module q
递归读取一些第三模块q
where q says requires transitive why and
q表示需要传递的原因，以及
now that X reads why why can say
现在，X知道了为什么可以说
requires transitive for some other
需要传递其他
module and X will read that too now be
模块和X现在也会阅读
careful once people require your module
一旦有人需要您的模块，请小心
explicitly you can refactor it downwards
明确地，您可以向下重构它
as much as you like but you cannot
尽可能多但不能
delete it there's no way for a module to
删除它是没有模块的
stand in for another module by taking
参加另一个模块
its name as an alias if someone requires
它的名称作为别名（如果有人需要）
X and X is deleted then the module
X和X被删除，然后该模块
system won't starts I said earlier that
系统无法启动我之前说过
the exports part of accessibility is
可访问性的出口部分是
pretty straightforward the packages
包非常简单
either exported or it isn't but it's
要么导出，要么不是，但是
actually a little more subtle than that
实际上比这更微妙
here are some of the exports of the
这是一些
java-based module exporting a package
基于Java的模块导出包
means that anyone can compile and run
意味着任何人都可以编译运行
against its public types and their
反对其公共类型及其
public elements
公共元素
there are dozens more packages in Java
Java中还有数十个软件包
base that aren't exported no one can
没有出口的基地
compile against their public types even
甚至针对他们的公共类型进行编译
if you make a class file by hand that
如果您手动制作课程文件，
refers to a public type in a non
指非公共类型
exported package it won't run this isn't
导出的程序包它将无法运行这不是
just compile time trickery the VMS doing
只是编译VMS做的时间欺骗
it as well but still that's all
它也一样，但仅此而已
accessibility in the Java language in
Java语言中的可访问性
VMware the accessing class and the
VMware访问类和
target class are known static leads it's
目标类是已知的静态线索
in the source code of the bytecode what
在字节码的源代码中是什么
about accessibility with reflection
关于反射的可访问性
where the target class is only known
仅知道目标类别的地方
dynamically we think it's very important
动态地我们认为这非常重要
that exporting a package like Java
导出像Java这样的包
security yep there is for static access
是的，安全是静态访问
to be programmed against does not mean
被编程反对并不意味着
that anyone can reflect over the
任何人都可以反思
internals of that package because if
该软件包的内部，因为如果
they can they will here is a stack
他们可以，他们会在这里是一个堆栈
overflow question from July 2016 someone
从2016年7月开始有人溢出问题
this is reven take a picture of URL
这是Reven拍摄的URL图片
someone was using set accessible to
有人正在使用可访问的集
access a private field in the class Java
访问类Java中的私有字段
security key store the purpose of the
安全密钥存储的目的
class Java security key store is and I
类Java安全密钥库是和我
quote a storage facility for
引用以下存储设备
cryptographic keys and certificates if
加密密钥和证书，如果
ever there was a class whose private
曾经有一个班级的私人
fields should be inaccessible it is this
字段应该无法访问，是这个
one now the Java security package is
现在的Java安全包是
exported so you can code against the
已导出，因此您可以针对
public type key store in its public
公共类型的公用密钥库
fields and methods not so that you can
字段和方法不能使您可以
reflect over clicky stores internals
反思clicky商店内部
ring code I love the the first answer
铃声我爱第一个答案
how ofter updating I something's not
如何更新我没有的东西
working how can I fix it you solve it by
工作如何解决它，您可以通过以下方式解决它
not fiddling with private data members
不摆弄私人数据成员
of other classes first answer so just
其他班级的第一答案就是
exporting a package exports P does not
出口包装出口P不
allow reflection to access the
允许反射访问
non-public elements of the package the
包的非公共元素
non-public types or even the
非公共类型甚至
the non pride that the non-public
非公开的非自豪
elements in public types so I said again
公共类型的元素，所以我再说一遍
if you obtain a class object for a non
如果您获得非
public type in the package you can still
包中的公共类型，您仍然可以
list its members but you cannot call
列出其成员，但您无法致电
gets or sets on its
获取或设置其
java.lang.reflect.method.invoke type
java.lang.reflect.method.invoke类型
similarly if you somehow obtained maybe
同样，如果您以某种方式获得了
someone passes it to you a Java Lang
有人将其传递给您一个Java Lang
reflect field object for a private field
反映私有字段的字段对象
in a public type you cannot call get or
在公共类型中，您不能调用get或
set on it and even calling said
放在上面，甚至打电话说
accessible won't help if the author of
如果作者是可访问的，将无济于事
the module really wants to allow access
该模块确实希望允许访问
to nonpublic elements via reflection
通过反射进入非公共元素
this can be expressed with exports
这可以用出口来表达
privates and that then allows reflection
私人，然后允许反思
to work as it did in jdk 8 private
像在jdk 8 private中一样工作
members of public types can be accessed
可以访问公共类型的成员
and public members of non-public types
和非公共类型的公共成员
we don't officially call it weak
我们没有正式称它为弱者
encapsulation but you can think of it
封装，但您可以想到
that way the bottom line is that strong
这样的底线是那么强大
encapsulation is even stronger than the
封装甚至比
powerful reflection capability is
强大的反射能力是
traditionally offered by the Java
传统上由Java提供
platform it's up to the module author to
平台，取决于模块作者
choose strong encapsulation and if they
选择强封装，如果他们选择
do via a plane exports as we do in Java
通过飞机出口来完成，就像我们在Java中一样
base there is no way for another module
没有其他模块的基础
to break in the module system API does
打破模块系统API的作用
not allow one module to augment the
不允许一个模块增加
exports of another module reflectively a
反射另一个模块的输出a
module can only X can only augment its
模块只能X只能增加其
own exports via the API so said
通过API自己导出，所以说
accessible behavior now depends on the
可访问的行为现在取决于
module authors choice of how a package
模块作者如何选择包装
is exported
出口
and of course for Java security public
当然，对于Java安全性公众
types no problem public methods in those
键入那些没有问题的公共方法
public types no problem code against
公共类型没有针对的问题代码
them but private things inside you can't
他们，但你里面的私人事物不能
touch them there is a question there are
碰他们有一个问题
lots of questions but I will take them
很多问题，但我会接受
at the end thank you accessibility used
最后谢谢您使用的辅助功能
to be a simple check basically for
基本上是一个简单的检查
public or same package at compile time
公共或相同的软件包在编译时
and around time in jdk 9 accessibility
并在jdk 9中可访问性
is the mechanism for strongly
是强力的机制
encapsulated module internals
封装的模块内部
accessibility relies on readability
可访问性取决于可读性
which can be direct or implied and
可以是直接的或暗示的
accessibility is enforced by the
可访问性由
compiler VM and reflection in line with
编译器VM和反射符合
the module declarations part 2
模块声明第2部分
everything so far has been about named
到目前为止，一切都与命名有关
modules modules explicitly declared with
用以下命令明确声明的模块
a name in module in photo java what
照片Java模块中的名称
about jar files on the classpath that
关于classpath上的jar文件
don't have a module in photo class file
照片类文件中没有模块
they seem to be in a world of their own
他们似乎处于自己的世界中
to keep the model of accessibility and
保持可访问性模型
readability consistence we introduce the
可读性一致性，我们介绍
unnamed module all classes not in named
未命名的模块所有未命名的类
modules are in the unnamed module it's
模块位于未命名的模块中
as if pay for it everything on the
好像为此付出了一切
classpath is in one big module and
classpath在一个大模块中，
because it's the module we can ask two
因为这是模块，我们可以问两个
questions what does it read and what
质疑它读什么，什么
does it exports what it reads is simple
它是否导出读取的内容很简单
every named module all of them as if by
每个命名模块都好像
magic for free this means anything
免费的魔术，这意味着一切
exported by a named module can be
可以通过命名模块导出
accessed by code in the unnamed module
通过未命名模块中的代码访问
you can turn a jar file into a named
您可以将一个jar文件转换为一个
module by adding module info doc class
通过添加模块信息doc类添加模块
and putting the jar on the module path
并将罐子放在模块路径上
when named modules are found
找到命名模块时
jars left on the classpath will not
保留在classpath上的jar不会
realize that anything happens they can
意识到发生任何事情他们都可以
still read those named modules that's a
仍然阅读那些命名模块
huge help for migration the next
下一个迁移的巨大帮助
question is what the unnamed module
问题是未命名的模块是什么
exports before that though we should ask
在此之前我们应该问一下出口
who reads the unnamed module remember
读未命名模块的人记得
our goal in the module system is
我们在模块系统中的目标是
reliable dependencies we believe very
我们相信非常可靠的依赖
strongly that named modules should not
强烈建议命名模块不应
read the unnamed module out of the box
开箱即用地读取未命名的模块
it would make a mockery of reliable
它会嘲笑可靠
dependencies to let named modules depend
让命名模块依赖的依赖项
on the arbitrary content of the
关于任意内容
classpath so you cannot write requires
classpath，所以你不能写要求
unnamed or requires classpath in module
未命名或模块中需要classpath
info java there are no reads edges going
信息java没有读取边缘
out to the unnamed module this seems
到未命名的模块，这似乎
like a huge hindrance for migration
像移民的巨大障碍
because any jar you turn into a named
因为任何罐子变成了一个
module can't access the jars left on the
模块无法访问左侧的jar
classpath the answer is automatic
classpath答案是自动的
modules you can take a jar say guava yah
你可以带一个罐子说番石榴模块
and move it from the classpath to the
并将其从类路径移至
module path that turns the jar into an
将罐子变成一个
automatic module that's all you have to
您只需要做的自动模块
do an automatic module is a named module
做一个自动模块就是一个命名模块
declared implicitly rather than
隐式声明而不是声明
explicitly its name is derived from its
明确地，其名称源自其名称
jar file name in obvious ways placing
jar文件名以明显的方式放置
guava jar on the module path gives an
模块路径上的番石榴罐给出了一个
automatic module called guava as before
像以前一样称为guava的自动模块
whenever you see a module you should ask
每当你看到一个模块，你应该问
what does it read and what does it
它读什么，它做什么
exports the automatic module guava reads
导出番石榴自动读取的模块
everything in the JDK and the unnamed
JDK中的所有内容以及未命名的
module it's as if it says requires
模块就好像要求
unnamed now the hindrance to migration
现在未命名迁移的障碍
is gone you can turn a jar into an
不见了，你可以把一个罐子变成一个
automatic module and it can still access
自动模块，它仍然可以访问
the jars left on the classpath we asked
我们问的类路径上剩下的罐子
earlier what the unnamed module exports
较早的未命名模块导出的内容
the answer is all its packages
答案是所有的包装
in ju najar and glass fish jar and
在ju najar和玻璃鱼缸中
hibernate jar precisely to help code in
休眠jar正是为了帮助代码
automatic modules which read the unnamed
读取未命名的自动模块
module and it's a it's a full power
模块，这是一个完整的力量
export as well you can reflect back in
导出以及您可以反映回去
because an automatic module is a real
因为自动模块是真实的
named module another named module can
命名模块另一个命名模块可以
require it suppose the my app module
假设我的应用程序模块需要它
says requires guava so there's a reads
说需要番石榴，所以读
edge then from my app to guava what does
然后从我的应用程序到番石榴边缘
an automatic module like guava exports
像番石榴出口这样的自动模块
that's easy all of its packages
这很容易
including for reflection so my app can
包括反思，这样我的应用程序就可以
access all of the public guava types and
访问所有公共番石榴类型和
reflect over it no problem my app could
反映它没有问题，我的应用程序可以
even say requires transitive guava to
甚至说需要传递番石榴来
transmit its dependency on guava up to
传输对番石榴的依赖
its own consumers so that anyone who
它自己的消费者，以便任何人
reads my app would read Wafaa for free
读取我的应用程序将免费读取Wafaa
even though guava is an automatic module
即使番石榴是自动模块
so by moving a jar from the classpath to
因此，通过将罐子从类路径移动到
the module path you get an automatic
您会自动获得模块路径
module that lets you start building up
使您可以开始构建的模块
your own graph of modules it's not
你自己的模块图不是
necessary to wait for every jar on the
有必要等待上的每个罐子
classpath to be modularized by its
类路径由其模块化
author before you start developing your
在开始开发您的作品之前
own modules that require it so there are
自己的模块需要它，所以有
three kinds of modules explicit named
三种模块的显式命名
modules like java sequel automatic named
像Java续集这样的模块自动命名
modules like guava and the unnamed
番石榴和未命名的模块
module aka the classpath and the key
模块又名classpath和密钥
point is there is lots of readability
重点是可读性强
for free to help with migration and
免费帮助迁移和
since the readability underpins the
因为可读性是
accessibility you then get a lot of
无障碍获取，然后您将获得很多
accessibility as you had on jelly aids
就像果冻辅助工具上的辅助功能
loaders and layers
装载机和层
I said before that strong encapsulation
我说过强封装之前
is independent of class loaders this
与类加载器无关
means that the model of class loading in
表示在
jdk 9 the model of class loading in jdk
jdk 9 jdk中的类加载模型
9 is unchanged the mechanism of loader
9不变的装载机机制
constraints for those of you who have
对于那些拥有
been reading the vm spec is unchanged
一直在阅读虚拟机规格不变
the notion of runtime packages is
运行时软件包的概念是
unchanged the java.lang class loader api
不变的java.lang类加载器api
is essentially unchanged class loading
本质上是不变的类加载
doesn't change in jdk 9 in addition the
除了在jdk 9中不变
actual class loaders the actual objects
实际的类加载器，实际的对象
in jdk 9 are the same as in jdk aids
jdk 9中的内容与jdk aid中的相同
there is the bootstrap loader there is
有引导加载程序
the platform loader used to be called
平台加载器曾经被称为
the extension loader too confusing call
扩展加载程序太混乱了
it the platform loader and then there is
它是平台加载程序，然后有
the application loader which loads
加载的应用程序加载器
everything on the classpath all on top
类路径上的所有内容都在顶部
of the vm traditionally the vast
传统上，
majority of JDK classes were defined by
大多数JDK类是由
the bootstrap loader critical JDK
引导加载程序关键JDK
modules such as Java base still have
Java base等模块仍然具有
their classes defined by the bootstrap
引导程序定义的类
loader for non-critical JDK modules it
非关键JDK模块的加载程序
is important for security to move their
对于移动他们的安全至关重要
classes out of the bootstrap loader if
引导加载程序之外的类，如果
possible modules in the bootstrap loader
引导加载程序中可能的模块
run with all permissions which is not
使用所有权限运行
ideal from a security perspective those
从安全角度来看，理想的是
modules can only be D privileged that is
模块只能获得D特权，即
run with fewer permissions if they're
如果使用较少的权限运行
not in the bootstrap loader so in jeddah
不在吉士大的引导加载程序中
k9 all the modules containing Java EE
k9包含Java EE的所有模块
technologies such as Java goober have
Java goober之类的技术具有
been moved as well as the JDBC modules
以及JDBC模块已被移走
Java sequel and Java sequel rosettes
Java续集和Java续集玫瑰花结
their classes are now defined by the
他们的类别现在由
platform loader frankly moving a module
平台装载器坦然地移动模块
as big as Java cawber 1831 classes and
和Java cawber 1831类一样大
31 exported packages is no small
31个导出包不小
accomplishment the D privileges were kid
D特权是孩子
self of specifying the fewer permissions
指定更少权限的自我
will continue for many years
将持续多年
the application loader is then
然后，应用程序加载器
responsible for everything else a number
对其他一切负责
of JDK tool modules such as JDK compiler
JDK工具模块（例如JDK编译器）
have their classes defined by the app
由应用定义其类
loader all classes in modules on the
加载模块上模块中的所有类
module path whether they're in a modular
模块路径，无论它们是否在模块化中
jar or in an automatic module like guava
jar或番石榴等自动模块中
are defined by the application loader
由应用程序加载程序定义
and all classes on the classpath in
以及classpath中的所有类
traditional jar files like jo nijar and
传统的jar文件，例如jo nijar和
glass fish jar are defined as before by
玻璃鱼缸的定义与以前相同
the application loader a couple of notes
应用程序加载器的一些注意事项
on compatibility first frameworks that
关于兼容性优先框架
delegates directly to the bootstrap
直接委托给引导程序
loader to find JDK classes might break
加载程序以查找JDK类可能会中断
on jdk nine because many jdk classes
在jdk 9上，因为许多jdk类
aren't there anymore frameworks should
不再有框架应该
use the new class loader method get'
使用新的类加载器方法get'
platform class loader which returns a
平台类加载器，返回一个
loader guaranteed to provide visibility
装载机保证提供可见度
of exported JDK classes second the
导出的JDK类的第二
application loader whilst there still is
仍然有应用程序加载器
one the object itself is no longer an
一个对象本身不再是一个
instance of URL class loader frameworks
URL类加载器框架的实例
that assume it is in order to hack via
假设它是为了通过
so accessible into its add URL method
可以访问其添加URL方法
sadface will break on jdk nine the only
sadface将会在9枚jdk上打破
supported way to dynamically extend the
支持的方式来动态扩展
class path is with the class path
类路径与类路径
attribute in jar files or with the agent
jar文件或代理中的属性
API and java.lang instruments now you
API和java.lang工具现在
may be wondering where the module system
可能想知道模块系统在哪里
itself lives in all of this it's
本身生活在这一切之中
important to realize where the module
重要的是要意识到模块在哪里
system isn't traditionally a module
传统上，系统不是模块
system was simply Java code that acted
系统只是起作用的Java代码
as a factory for class loaders it
作为装载机的工厂
created loaders that defined classes
创建定义类的加载器
found in some modular artifacts and then
在一些模块化工件中找到，然后
those load is delegated to each other in
这些负载在
accordance with some kind of modular
按照某种模块化
imports and exports as I mentioned
我提到的进出口
before there is then some encapsulate
在有封装之前
for classes because those loaders a B
上课，因为那些装载机是B
and C can hide classes they can isolate
C可以隐藏他们可以隔离的类
classes from each other a module system
相互分类的模块系统
that does this will still work on jdk
这样做仍然可以在jdk上工作
nine because class loading hasn't
九是因为没有上课
changed but the module system in jdk
更改了，但jdk中的模块系统
nine is quite different the module
九是完全不同的模块
system in jdk nine is not a factory for
JDK 9中的系统不是工厂
class loaders but rather a conduit a
类装载机，而是管道
transmission mechanism that allows
传输机制允许
modules to be communicated to the vm
与虚拟机通信的模块
whoever creates the class loaders is
创建类加载器的人是
responsible for using the module system
负责使用模块系统
API to transmit module names contents
用于传输模块名称内容的API
dependencies and exports to the vm
依赖关系并导出到vm
that's how the vm knows enough to
这就是虚拟机足够了解的方式
enforce accessibility it's also how the
强制执行可访问性，这也是
core reflection API can enforce
核心反射API可以强制执行
accessibility since core reflection is
可访问性，因为核心反射是
based on vm provided class objects you
基于vm提供的类对象
can think of the java launcher as
可以认为Java启动器是
creating three loaders and doing the
创建三个加载程序并执行
transmission down to the vm for modules
向下传输到模块的vm
on the module path you can see why we
在模块路径上，您可以看到为什么我们
wanted the module system to be
希望模块系统成为
disinterested in class loaders the JDK
对类加载器JDK不感兴趣
has been factored into dozens of modules
已经分解成数十个模块
but it's class loading architecture the
但它是类加载架构
shape of the class learning architecture
课堂学习架构的形状
hasn't changed encapsulation is provided
没有更改提供的封装
by trouve e.m level accessibility not by
烦恼em级别的可访问性，而不是
class loader based visibility so the
基于类加载器的可见性，因此
module system doesn't need to mandates
模块系统不需要强制要求
one loader per module it can handle
每个模块可以处理一个装载程序
multiple modules per loader just fine
每个加载程序有多个模块就可以了
that's what the picture shows you'll
这就是图片所显示的
recall that I talked earlier about the
回想一下我之前谈到的
unnamed module as a vehicle for
未命名模块作为车辆
compatibility strictly speaking I was
兼容性严格来说我是
referring to the unnamed module of the
指的是未命名的模块
application loader in fact every class
应用程序加载器实际上是每个类
every class loader has an unnamed module
每个类加载器都有一个未命名的模块
if the vm sees a class being defined by
如果vm看到由定义的类
a loader and the vm
加载程序和虚拟机
associate that class with a named module
将该类与命名模块关联
that was transmitted down earlier then
那是早些时候传下来的
the vm treats the class as being in the
虚拟机将类视为
loaders unnamed module as you might
装载程序未命名模块
guess the vm always allows access to
猜测虚拟机始终允许访问
public classes in an unnamed module this
未命名模块中的公共类this
means this all means that every class
意味着这一切意味着每堂课
every class is a member of a module even
每个类甚至是模块的成员
classes in the jar files on the
jar文件上的类
classpath j unit jar and glassfish top
classpath j罐子和玻璃鱼顶
jar are members of a module that it's
jar是它的模块成员
actually the it's meant to be the
实际上，这意味着
seventh box in the vm on the right and
右侧虚拟机中的第七个框
if you have a class object the get
如果您有一个类对象，则获取
module method will always return a
模块方法将始终返回
sensible module object the module system
明智的模块对象模块系统
introduces the concept of a layer to
将层的概念引入
associate class loaders with modules a
将类加载器与模块关联
layer is a family of class loaders that
层是一类的类加载器
together serve to load classes for a
一起为一个类加载类
graph of modules logically the java
Java逻辑上的模块图
launcher defines the boot layer
启动器定义启动层
consisting of the three familiar loaders
由三个熟悉的装载机组成
it's the boot layer that associates the
是引导层将
java base and java logging modules with
Java基础和Java日志记录模块
the bootstrap loader the java sequel and
引导程序Java续集和
java korba modules with the platform
Java Korba模块与平台
loader and so on so a layer is created
加载程序等，以便创建一个图层
from two things graph of modules and a
从两个模块的图和一个
function that maps modules two loaders
映射模块两个加载器的功能
on the left is the graph from resolving
左边是解析的图形
the JDK j-link module which contains the
JDK j-link模块，其中包含
jailing tool for building runtime jeddak
用于构建运行时jeddak的jaail工具
8 images just an example of a module
8张图像只是一个模块的示例
graph on the right is a lambda
右边的图是lambda
expression mapping some of the modules
表达式映射某些模块
in that graph to the bootstrap loader
在该图中引导加载程序
and the application loader creating a
然后应用程序加载器创建一个
layer informs the module system about
层通知模块系统有关
the packages that will exist in the
将存在于
program and the modules they'll come
程序以及它们将要出现的模块
from this is a great slide to take a
这是一张很棒的幻灯片
picture of hint hint
提示图片提示图片
the module system passes this
模块系统通过了
information to the vm so that when
信息到虚拟机，以便何时
classes are eventually loaded and
最终加载类并
defined the vm knows which module a
定义了vm知道哪个模块
class belongs to and what that module
类属于那个模块
reads and exports it's like the vm has a
读取并导出，就像虚拟机有一个
shadow copy of the module graph that it
它的模块图的影子副本
uses when checking accessibility between
在检查之间的可访问性时使用
classes now because of how class loading
现在上课，因为如何加载类
works the module system must enforce
模块系统必须执行的工作
certain constraints on a layers module
图层模块上的某些约束
graph and on a layers mapping from
图形和从
modules to loaders let's talk about the
加载程序的模块让我们谈谈
graph first last chance to take a
图的最后一次机会
picture and slide at the back very good
图片和背面滑动很好
Oh bit more or more okay this is the
哦，或多或少，好吧，这是
graph of modules in jeddah k9 what do
吉达k9中的模块图
you notice about it it's a dag exactly
您会注意到这完全是个问题
the same arts that came from over there
来自那边的同样的艺术
last year I remember so such a precise
去年我记得这么精确
answer okay it's a directed directed is
回答好吧，这是有针对性的
a directed acyclic graph no cycles this
有向无环图
is the first and biggest constraint on a
是第一个也是最大的约束
module graph it's taken almost a decade
模块图花了将近十年
to detangle the tens of thousands of
纠缠成千上万
classes in the JDK to the acyclic and
JDK中的非循环类
relatively sane state that you see here
你在这里看到的相对理智的状态
we'd like to keep it that way in fact
我们实际上希望保持这种方式
one of the motivations for investing in
投资的动机之一
modularization of a code base is the
代码库的模块化是
knowledge that once completes there
一旦完成的知识
won't be any backsliding into the ball
不会向后退
of mudd's the cyclic dependencies allow
的循环依赖
we're not the only ones who think like
我们并不是唯一一个像
this java application architecture is an
这个Java应用程序架构是
outstanding book about modularity in a
关于模块化的杰出著作
section titled cyclic dependences the
循环依赖部分
death knell it says excessive dependence
丧钟说过度依赖
is about but cyclic dependencies are
是关于但循环依赖
especially bad
特别糟糕
it goes on to say generally speaking
一般说来
cycles are always bad however some
周期总是不好，但是有些
cycles are worse than others cycles
周期比其他周期差
among classes are tolerable assuming
类之间是可以容忍的
they don't cause cycles among the
它们不会导致
packages or modules containing them
包含它们的软件包或模块
cycles among packages may also be
包之间的周期也可能是
tolerable tolerable assuming they don't
可以容忍的，假设他们没有
cause cycles among the modules
导致模块之间的循环
containing them module relationships
包含它们之间的模块关系
must never be cyclic this book is from
永远不要循环，这本书来自
years ago nothing to do with the Java
多年前与Java无关
module system but this is good advice
模块系统，但这是一个很好的建议
let's turn to another constraint on
让我们转向另一个约束
module graphs the second constraint on
模块绘制第二个约束图
the module graph that's going to be the
模块图将是
foundation of the layer is that a module
该层的基础是模块
must read only one module that exports a
必须仅读取一个导出
package of a given name if a module
给定名称的包（如果有模块）
could read more than one module that
可以读取多个模块，
exports p as x is trying to do here in
出口p作为x试图在这里做
which module would P be accessed there's
P将访问哪个模块
no answer the module graph is just
没有答案模块图只是
broken so we defend against that only
坏了，所以我们只能防御
module graphs which obey this
遵从此的模块图
constraints and have no cycles can be
约束，没有周期可以
turned into a layer that's really what
变成了真正的一层
we mean by reliable dependencies
我们的意思是可靠的依赖
dependencies are reliable when a module
模块依赖时可靠
can access only one version of a package
只能访问软件包的一个版本
at a time there are no split packages
一次没有拆分包
like you get when multiple jars on the
就像当多个罐子放在
classpath contain potentially different
类路径可能包含不同的内容
versions of the same package now you
现在，同一软件包的版本
might be wondering if it's possible for
可能想知道是否有可能
X to read version 1 of Y while at the
X在时读取Y的版本1
same time another module reads version 2
同时另一个模块读取版本2
of why after all X and the other module
毕竟X和其他模块的原因
would each read only one module
每个将只读取一个模块
exporting p the answer is that it's not
导出p的答案是，不是
possible because it can only work safely
可能因为它只能安全​​地工作
in certain scenarios and outside those
在某些情况下以及那些情况之外
scenarios it's not clear that supporting
方案尚不清楚
it out of the box which is to say in the
开箱即用
Java launch
Java启动
the one that creates the class loaders
创建类加载器的那个
it's not clear that supporting it out
尚不清楚是否支持它
the box is worthwhile but you can all
盒子值得，但你可以
ask for questions about that in ten
十个问题
minutes time recall that a layer
分钟时间回想起一层
includes a module graph for which we saw
包括我们看到的模块图
two constraints and a mapping from
两个约束和一个映射
modules two loaders the main constraint
模块两个装载机的主要约束
on the mapping is that if different
在映射上是如果不同
modules in the graph have a class called
图中的模块有一个名为
C then those modules must be mapped to
C然后必须将这些模块映射到
different loaders this is the
不同的装载机，这是
fundamental limit in class loading a
类加载的基本限制
class loader can only create one class
类加载器只能创建一个类
called see more conservatively we say
叫保守地说，我们说
that if different modules have the same
如果不同的模块具有相同的
package not just class then those
包装不仅是类，还有那些
modules must be mapped to different
模块必须映射到不同的
loaders of the layer the mapping from
映射的图层的加载器
modules two loaders has another
模块两个装载机有另一个
constraint that's not practical to check
检查不实际的约束
though because it concerns how load is
虽然因为它涉及负载如何
behavior on time it's that the loaders
准时的行为是装载机
must delegate to each other in
必须互相委托
accordance with the reads edges of the
根据阅读的边缘
module graph the reason is obvious if
模块图的原因很明显，如果
module X reads module y then in order
模块X依次读取模块y
for X's classes in one loader to access
X的类在一个加载器中访问
wise classes in another loader X's
另一个加载程序X中的明智类
loader must delegate to wise loader just
加载程序必须委派给明智的加载程序
just to find the classes even before you
只是为了在您之前找到课程
can start worrying about access as their
可以开始担心访问权限
name suggests layers can be layered when
名称表明可以在以下情况下分层
a graph of modules is resolved it's
一个模块图就解决了
actually resolved against a parent layer
实际针对父层解决
then when the graph helps to create a
然后当图形有助于创建一个
new layer the new layer picks up the
新层新层接
parent layer this allows a graph of
父层，这允许
modules to have dangling references that
具有悬挂引用的模块
is requires clauses for modules that the
是模块的require子句，
module system will find in a parent
模块系统将在父级中找到
layer during resolution on the Left
分辨率期间在左图层
resolution has set up not only a reads
分辨率不仅设置为读取
edge between mott between modules in one
模块之间的莫特之间的边缘
layer the horizontal one but also a
将水平层也分层
reads edge between modules in different
读取不同模块之间的边缘
layers constructing a tree of layers in
层构建中的层树
this fashion is the job of a
这种时尚是一个人的工作
framework like an app server or a test
应用服务器或测试之类的框架
harness layers give frameworks
线束层提供框架
tremendous freedom to organize modules
极大地自由地组织模块
at runtime without upsetting the
在运行时不会破坏
frameworks traditional use of class
框架传统使用类
loaders it's like the invoke dynamic
加载程序就像动态调用
instruction from jdk 7 away for
来自JDK 7的指令
framework developers to interact with
框架开发人员进行交互
the vm to reify information about the
虚拟机来验证有关
shape of a program let's look at one
程序的形状让我们来看一个
scenario where layers help out layers
图层帮助图层的场景
are how the module system supports
系统如何支持
multiple versions of the module here an
该模块的多个版本
app server has created two layers on top
应用服务器在顶部创建了两层
of the boot layer on the left the Hadoop
Hadoop左侧的启动层
player reifies a module graph with guava
播放器使用番石榴校正模块图
version 11 and jackson version 1 and on
版本11和杰克逊版本1及更高版本
the right the JavaScript layer reifies a
右边的JavaScript层将
module graph with guava version 18 and
番石榴18和版本的模块图
jackson version 2 each module graph is
杰克逊版本2每个模块图是
well-formed and mapped to loaders in a
格式正确并映射到
sensible way but the modules in the
明智的方式，但在模块
Hadoop layer are not aware of the
Hadoop层不知道
modules in the JavaScript layer and vice
JavaScript层中的模块，反之
versa but please note this is all thanks
反之亦然，但请注意，这一切都是感谢
to a framework creating the Hadoop and
到创建Hadoop的框架，以及
JavaScript layers the java launcher
JavaScript将Java启动器分层
doesn't create layers like this all it
不会像这样创建图层
does is resolve the module you give on
这样做是解决您给的模块
the command line then map everything in
然后在命令行中映射所有内容
the resulting module graph to the
结果模块图
application loader in the boot layer it
应用程序加载器在启动层吗
supports only one version of each module
每个模块仅支持一个版本
the reason is to avoid the nightmarish
原因是为了避免噩梦
problems that occur when multiple
多个时发生的问题
versions of a module or indeed any jar
模块的版本或实际上任何jar
casually come into contact with each
随便与每个人接触
other it's really only safe to use
其他真的只有安全使用
multiple versions of the module when a
一个模块的多个版本
framework like an app server is in
像应用程序服务器这样的框架
control the takeaway is this just as
控制外卖就是这样
modules wrap up coherent sets of
模块包装了相关的集合
packages and interact with the VMS
打包并与VMS交互
accessibility mechanism layers wrap up
可访问性机制层总结
coherent sets of modules and interact
连贯的模块集并进行交互
with the class loader visibility
具有类加载器的可见性
mechanism it'll be up to frameworks to
机制取决于框架
use of layers in the next 20 years just
在未来20年内仅使用图层
as they made use of class loaders in
因为他们在
javas first 20 years I urge any
Java前20年我强烈要求
framework developers watching to open up
框架开发人员正在观察开放
the JDK 9 Javadoc and look at java.lang
JDK 9 Javadoc并查看java.lang
module configuration and
模块配置和
java.lang.reflect.method.invoke then
然后调用java.lang.reflect.method.invoke
control the relationship between modules
控制模块之间的关系
a graph of modules and the class loaders
模块图和类加载器
and assuming class loaders respect the
并假设装载机尊重
module graph that is they delegate
他们委托的模块图
sensibly the system is safe by
明智的做法是通过
construction there are no cycles or
施工没有周期或
split packages zooming all the way out
拆分包装，一直缩小
here are the three key points there is
这是三个关键点
strong encapsulation of modules by the
模块对模块的强力封装
compiler vm and core reflection there
编译器vm和核心反射在那里
are unnamed and automatic modules to
是未命名的自动模块
help with migration and the whole system
帮助迁移和整个系统
is safe by construction no cycles or
施工安全无循环
split packages in essence the module
本质上将包拆分为模块
system is a seat belt not a jetpack if
系统是安全带，不是喷气背包，如果
this reminds you of the rationale for
这使您想起了
generics 15 years of more than 15 years
仿制药15年以上的15年
ago your rights writing a module
之前您编写模块的权利
declaration makes your code more
声明使您的代码更加
reliable and maintainable much like
可靠和可维护的，就像
writing a list of string rather than
写一个字符串列表而不是
lists you always knew that your list
列出您一直都知道的清单
held strings and generics let you to
持有的字符串和泛型可以让您
know that you always knew that a package
知道你一直都知道一个包裹
was not for general use and modules let
不能用于一般用途，而让模块
you to know that it's no coincidence
你知道这不是巧合
that designing a practical module system
设计实用的模块系统
and modular rising the JDK has taken
和JDK采取的模块化崛起
approximately as long as designing the
大约只要设计
pragmatic generic type system and genera
语用通用类型系统和属
fiying the JDK there's still a long road
克服JDK，还有很长的路要走
head although the module system is
头虽然模块系统是
conceptually simple there are changes in
概念上很简单
jdk 9 that probably won't break music
可能不会破坏音乐的jdk 9
but might break framework code and I'd
但可能会破坏框架代码，我会
like to go through them quickly there
喜欢在那里快速通过他们
are three areas of incompatibility in
是三个不兼容的领域
jdk nine connected with the official
JDK九连官方
definition of java SE first we've
首先定义Java SE
removed six methods from the packages
从软件包中删除了六种方法
java.util logging and Java util jar
java.util日志记录和Java util jar
their signatures made the Java base
他们的签名成为Java的基础
module depend on the Java desktop module
模块取决于Java桌面模块
and no one wants that this removal was
而且没有人希望这是
announced in the umbrella jsr se8 in
在雨伞jsr se8中宣布
2014 in addition we've removed to a WT
此外，2014年我们已移至WT
packages that were never supported on
从未支持的软件包
the right there despite being in the
尽管在那里
Java namespace very sad face second the
Java命名空间非常可悲第二
Java EE types shipped with the JDK are
JDK附带的Java EE类型是
not accessible by default this means
默认情况下无法访问
korba Jack's be jax-ws the Java
korba杰克的jax-ws Java
activation framework and the JD kaise
激活框架和JD kaise
subsets of the Java transaction API and
Java交易API的子集和
the common annotations API the types are
常见的注释API类型是
physically in the JDK image but their
物理上在JDK映像中，但是
modules are not read by the unnamed
未命名的模块不会读取模块
module of the app loader if you're
应用加载程序的模块（如果您要
writing a module no problem just require
编写模块没问题，只需要
java koerber or Java XML bind or
java koerber或Java XML绑定或
whatever but if you're running code from
不管是什么，但是如果您正在从以下位置运行代码
the classpath you need a command-line
您需要命令行的类路径
flag to activate the EE modules third
标记以激活EE模块
the version strings reported by the
版本报告的版本字符串
system properties Java specification
系统属性Java规范
version Java VM version Java VM
版本Java VM版本Java VM
specification version etc have changed
规格版本等已更改
code that looks for one dots at the
在代码中寻找一个点的代码
beginning of the string will fail on jdk
字符串的开头将在jdk上失败
nine because the version strings begin
九，因为版本字符串开始
with nine there are then three areas of
有九个则有三个区域
incompatibility within the jdk nine
jdk九内不兼容
implementation first we've slimmed down
实施首先我们精简了
the Sun misc package some miss gun safe
太阳杂物包装有些枪支小姐
is still accessible but some misc base64
仍可访问，但有些杂项base64
encoder and some misc base64 decoder are
编码器和一些其他base64解码器是
gone
不见了
one thing you can do today is run the
您今天可以做的一件事就是运行
Jade EPS tool that came with jdk 8 over
jdk 8随附的Jade EPS工具
all of your jars it'll tell you if
你所有的罐子都会告诉你
they're using unofficial classes like
他们正在使用诸如
some misc bake 64 encoder and then
一些杂项烘烤64编码器，然后
recommend official replacements like the
建议像这样的官方替代品
java.util base64 class introduced in jdk
jdk中引入的java.util base64类
8 seconds many jdk internal api's are
8秒很多jdk内部api
not exported code that tries to access
未导出尝试访问的代码
even public types in the sun net www
甚至公共类型在阳光网www
package or sun security x509 or Khamsin
包装或防晒x509或Khamsin
ork apache xerxes internal jacks p I
ork apache xerxes内部插孔p I
could go on will fail with an illegal
可能会继续下去，并因非法而失败
access error the only way to regain
访问错误是重新获得的唯一方法
access is with a command-line flag third
访问带有命令行标志
many internal aspects of the JDK have
JDK的许多内部方面
been overhauled such as the layout on
大修，如布局
disk and the implementation of the three
磁盘与执行三
class loaders code that assumes there's
假定存在
a file called RT jar or tools jar in a
一个名为RT jar或tools jar的文件
particular directory will fail on JD k9
特定目录在JD k9上将失败
scripts that try to patch the JDK with
尝试使用以下命令修补JDK的脚本
minus X boot class pass / p for pre pens
减去X引导类通行证/预支笔p
will fail on jdk nine and as i mentioned
会在9英镑兑美元失败，正如我提到的
before code that assumes the application
假定应用程序的代码之前
loader is instance of URL class loader
loader是URL类loader的实例
or that assumes all jdk classes are
或假设所有jdk类都是
defined by the bootstrap loader will
引导加载程序定义的将
fail on JD k9 the module system itself
在JD k9模块系统本身上失败
tries hard to support migration but it
尽力支持迁移，但是
takes only one unmaintained library to
只需要一个未维护的库即可
prevent migration to jdk 9 if that
防止迁移到jdk 9
library can't migrate because it's using
库正在迁移，因为它正在使用
something in comms on all / patches axes
所有/修补程序轴上的通讯内容
internal checks p then nothing on top of
内部检查p然后什么也没有
it can migrate to being a module either
它可以迁移为模块
in this regard modules are unusual they
在这方面，模块是不寻常的
suffer from a tragedy of the Commons
遭受公地悲剧
whereas most big features like generics
而大多数大功能（如泛型）
or lambdas let people opt-in at their
或lambdas让人们选择加入
own pace without needing to wait for
自己的节奏，无需等待
others last slide as i said the single
正如我说的那样，其他人最后一张幻灯片
best thing you can do to prepare for
您可以做的最好的准备
jetty canine is fire up JDK 8 and run
码头犬正在启动JDK 8并运行
the Jade EPS tool which analyzes
进行分析的Jade EPS工具
dependences it can tell you if your co
依赖关系可以告诉您您的合作伙伴
or code that you rely on will be
或您依赖的代码将是
affected by the changes in 9 please try
受9中更改的影响，请尝试
the JDK 9 early access binaries on
上的JDK 9早期访问二进制文件
java.net the module system has been
java.net的模块系统已经
present and active doing the
现在和积极做
encapsulation for the JDK modules since
自JDK模块的封装以来，
March twenty sixteen plus the J depth
3月26日加J深度
tool in jdk nine is more accurate than
JDK 9中的工具比
the one in jdk 8 everything you ever
jdk 8中的一个，您所拥有的一切
wanted to know about the module system
想了解模块系统
including much of what I've said here is
包括我在这里所说的很多
discussed in JEP 261 I cannot emphasize
我不能强调在JEP 261中讨论的内容
enough how much valuable information is
有多少有价值的信息
inject 261 there's also JEP 260 which
注入261还有JEP 260
defines those JDK internal classes to be
定义那些JDK内部类为
exposed in jdk nine and JEP 223 which
暴露在jdk 9和JEP 223中
defines the new version strings
定义新版本的字符串
beginning nine dots and JEP 220 which
开头的九个点和JEP 220
describes how are ter has gone away and
描述三人如何消失，
finally JEP 200 gives an overview of the
最后，JEP 200概述了
JDK modules but if you've already read
JDK模块，但如果您已经阅读过
JEP 261 there won't be any surprises in
JEP 261不会有任何惊喜
200 and with that at fifty-six minutes
200，并在第五十六分钟
thank you very much
非常感谢你
and we will take questions I think we've
我们会提出我认为我们已经提出的问题
got become to 15 minutes someone has
到了15分钟
been charging their iphone no wonder it
一直在为他们的iphone充电
went so slowly everything was so if you
进行得如此缓慢如果您一切顺利
have question please come up to the
有问题请提出
front we cannot hear you if you stand
前面，如果你站着，我们听不见你的声音
where you are I promise we're not making
你在哪里我保证我们不会
it up we can't hear you so if you have a
我们听不到您的声音，所以如果您有
question please come and use this mic
问题，请过来使用此麦克风
here is it a different question than the
这是一个不同于
ones you've asked before yeah it's
是你之前问过的
different so one thing that I've always
不同，所以我一直都在做一件事
found odd in tomcat they try to prevent
在tomcat中发现奇怪之处，他们试图防止
classloader d-league's by knowing out
通过了解Classloader D联盟
all static fields when you unload a web
卸载网站时的所有静态字段
app I'm assuming that won't work anymore
我认为这将不再起作用的应用程序
it will work if they do the right thing
如果他们做对了就行
how do they make that happen because
他们如何做到这一点，因为
they're loading the classes the Tomcat
他们正在加载Tomcat类
if if the web app is itself a module but
如果网络应用本身是一个模块，但是
all of its classes are loaded by tom cat
它的所有类均由tom cat加载
tom cat is a deity it can rewrite module
汤姆猫是神，它可以重写模块
declarations on the way in it can choose
声明方式可以选择
to export to just to itself by the way
顺便出口到自己
or to one of its modules any packages it
或其任何模块将其打包到其模块之一
needs to reflect over although whether
需要反思，虽然是否
it actually needs to do what you've just
它实际上需要做你刚刚做的
said sounds like an optimization that
说听起来像是一个优化
you may not need on its mike on yeah
您可能不需要对它的麦克风
there's also a specific list of issues
还有一个具体的问题清单
in quotes that Tomcat has with the JDK
Tomcat对JDK的引用
and where it's gone into the JDK and all
以及它进入JDK的位置以及所有
doubt fields and things like that many
怀疑领域和诸如此类的事情
of those issues have actually already
这些问题实际上已经
been addressed and in fact over the last
已经解决，实际上在过去
couple of bills there are some specific
几张账单有一些具体的
fixes in the JDK specifically for these
在JDK中专门针对这些进行了修复
type of issues that Tomcat and ran into
Tomcat遇到的问题类型
thank you that actually the maintainer
谢谢你，实际上是维护者
zuv Tomcat I think Mark Thomas in
zuv Tomcat，我认为Mark Thomas在
particular has been proactive in
特别是在
actually finding these issues and
实际上发现这些问题，
sending bug reports
发送错误报告
the person who had a question there is
有问题的人是
left so that was a successful strategy
离开，那是一个成功的策略
yes what is going to be the fate of
是的，这将是命运
shaded jars and uber jars where's Robert
阴影罐子和超级罐子，罗伯特在哪里
oh it's right behind you a question for
哦，就在您身后
me them I don't know ask the maven the
我他们我不知道问行家
committer say someone it's not only a
提交人说某人不仅是
maid problem it's about sharing it about
女佣的问题是关于分享
correct creating the uber jar and there
正确创建超级罐子
you have all the classes just inside one
您将所有课程都放在一个内
jar so you have lost your encapsulation
罐子，所以您失去了封装
so I know that mark has one thing about
所以我知道商标与
that only his issue list so which is to
那只是他的问题清单，所以
wait for an answer a life or a proposal
等待答案的生活或建议
for it
为了它
ha no more questions ah ok please Wow
哈没有其他问题啊，好的，哇
we've really raised the barrier to entry
我们确实提高了进入壁垒
is very high so no one has questions
很高，所以没有人有疑问
anymore can you give an example i canna
你能再举一个例子吗？
site you have here what would manage
您在这里有什么网站可以管理
like the this Hadoop layer this
就像这个Hadoop层
JavaScript layer Tomcats I mean it it's
JavaScript层Tomcats我的意思是
hard to get across how disinterested we
很难理解我们多么无私
are in class loaders if you're a
如果您是
framework that spinning loaders today it
今天旋转装载机的框架
all still works v you can even know you
一切仍然有效v你甚至可以知道你
can even load classes from modular jar
甚至可以从模块化jar中加载类
files if you're if you're all the
文件，如果你是全部
framework and you're ignoring the module
框架，而您忽略了该模块
in photo class file ok that's your
在照片课程文件中，好，这是您的
lookout but if you want to respect the
out望台，但如果您想尊重
modular dependencies and encapsulation
模块化依赖关系和封装
that the web app code itself write it up
Web应用程序代码本身将其编写出来
to the container to not ignore module in
到容器中不要忽略模块
federal class files to load them and
联邦级文件以加载它们并
when you load them the whole point is
当您加载它们时，整个要点是
that a module says not only would
一个模块说不仅
exports board it depends on and
出口局取决于
hopefully tom cat will be able to call
希望汤姆猫能够打电话
the module system API to resolve those
模块系统API来解决这些问题
dependencies and spin up a small layer
依赖并旋转一小层
with exactly the same class though does
与完全相同的类
it had before but with the classes of
它曾经有过，但有
that loader now known to be members of a
该装载机现在已知是
module the module to load a mapping told
模块加载映射的模块告诉
to this new layer so the the graph of
到这个新层，所以图
class odors will look the same at
类气味看起来相同
runtime if you could visualize it so
运行时（如果可以这样可视化）
someone else a part of us is do you
别人是我们的一部分吗
export resources then to or do they
然后将资源导出到或做
follow the same rules yes there are some
遵循相同的规则是的
rules about which resources you the
关于您使用哪些资源的规则
exports keyword is for pentax package
出口关键字是宾得包
names this is a good question it doesn't
命名这是一个好问题，不是
you don't specify resources like that
你没有这样指定资源
but they are mostly ex the useful
但它们大多是有用的
resources are exported for reflective
导出资源以进行反思
access which is how you get to them
访问方式是如何到达他们的
right yes so Julie in like a you know
是的，所以朱莉像你一样知道
sometimes you put resources in a like
有时候你把资源放在一个
the same names places your package
相同的名称放置您的包裹
others
其他
I don't just kind of like invention so
我不只是喜欢发明
does everything now need to be in a Java
现在一切都需要在Java中完成
package I know oh no no you can still
包裹，我知道哦，不，不，你仍然可以
have your resources in Metron and what's
在Metron中拥有您的资源，这是什么
the rule for whether they're exported an
是否将其导出的规则
arts if there if there are namespace of
艺术，如果有的话
maps to the package then there has to be
映射到包，那么必须有
exported if you've been in top-level
如果您已经进入顶级，则导出
packages that are certain that are in
确定在的软件包
top-level directories aren't really
顶级目录不是真的
packages like meta-inf is not a valid
像meta-inf这样的软件包无效
package name then they've just continue
包名称，然后他们继续
to be be able to locate and access them
能够找到并访问它们
as as you always did all right just
就像您一向做的一样
under two exceptional yes there's in the
在两个例外的情况下，
updated proposal there is a specific
更新的提案中有一个具体的
exception for doc class files because
doc类文件的异常，因为
there's many many to you toons need to
有很多很多你需要卡通
access class files so they just worked
访问类文件，以便它们可以正常工作
can I just say one thing just about the
我可以只说一件事吗
layers on your first first party a
在第一方的第一层上
question is it doesn't actually require
问题是它实际上并不需要
a sophisticated app server to use layers
复杂的应用服务器以使用图层
is actually many tools might even may
实际上有很多工具甚至可能
actually use layers as well so for
实际也使用图层
example the Java C compiler loads
Java C编译器加载的示例
annotation processors that are deployed
部署的注释处理器
as modules in their own layer the
作为各自层中的模块
jailing tool can has it has a plug-in
jaail工具可以有一个插件
interface you can actually deploy and
您可以实际部署的界面
plugins as modules and and they will
插件作为模块，他们将
actually be loaded into their own layer
实际上被加载到自己的图层中
yeah thats its parented to the boot lair
是的，这就是靴巢的父母
so there's many many tools okay we're
所以有很多工具可以
all done
全部做完